Guide to the Yale School of Drama Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the dean, 1985-1990; Accession 1991-A-050
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
    - The Piano Lesson (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Two Trains Running (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Fences (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The Tempest (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Joe Turner's Come and Gone (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1987-1988 Season
    - Sarcophagus (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Melons (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Piano Lesson (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Winterfest 8 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Winterfest 8 Seminars (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - The Miser (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - O'Neill Project (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1988-1989 Season
    - The Warrior Ant (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Intermezzo (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Kiss of the Spider Woman (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Kiss of the Spider Woman: Post-Rep (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - The Alchemist (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Winterfest 9 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Winterfest 9 Seminars (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Moon over Miami (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Moon over Miami: Letters (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Cobb (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Playboy of the Western World (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1989-1990 Season
    - Solid Gold Cadillac (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Miss Julie (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Summer and Smoke (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Winterfest 10 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Troilus and Cressida (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Pygmalion (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Yale School of Drama
    - Pericles, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Titus Andronicus, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Students, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Course Proposals (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Interim Financial Reports (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Summer Payments (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Thesis Projects (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Verse Projects (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Yale University
    - Capital Planning (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Commencement, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Giamatti Memorial (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - School of Music (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Union Negotiations, Yale (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Association of Yale Alumni QE 11 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Contact Sheets, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - NPC Administrator (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - The Road to Mecca (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - A Walk in the Woods (Russia), 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - University Theatre Seating Platforms (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Moon over Miami (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Playboy of the Western Indies (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - King John / As You Like It (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Yale: South Africa Investments (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Yale: Students, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Two Trains Running (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - A-E, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 70 - 72)
    - A Better Chance ABC (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - AIDS Benefit, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - All-American Collegiate Golf (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Amistad Committee (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Arts-in-Education (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Black Masks (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Connecticut Arts Endowment Funding (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Connecticut Commission on the Arts (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Development
    - Annual Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Combustion Engineering (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Connecticut National Bank (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Eldon Elder Associates (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Leigh, Nitch and Abby (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Universal Pictures (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Drama League of New York (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Emerge Magazine (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Ensemble Theatre Company (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - F-K, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 95 - 97)
    - Golden Boy (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Hartford Courant (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - International Women Playwrights Conference (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - L-Q, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 105 - 107)
    - Liverpool Playhouse (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - National Endowment for the Arts: Hodsoll, Frank (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - National Endowment for the Arts / NCA Resolution (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - National Theatre Conference (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - New Haven Public Schools (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - New Jersey State Council on the Arts (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - O'Neill Theater Center (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - R-Z, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 120 - 122)
    - Reinhart, Richard (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Soviet Managers (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Stanislavski Center (Box 3, Folder 126)
- Records of the dean, 1965-1991; Accession 1992-A-012
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2026
  - A - B, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Actors Equity Association, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Albertus Magnus College, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arena Stage, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Black Filmmakers Hall of Fame, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Brustein, Robert, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - C - D, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Columbia University, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Common Wealth Awards, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut Bar Association, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Delphi International, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - DePaul University, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Development
    - Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Directors Guild of America, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Drama Desk, Inc., 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dramatists Guild, Inc., 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - E - F, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Eastern Area Links, Inc., 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Fisher, Craig, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - (My English Name is Patience) Fugard The Road to Mecca, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - G - H, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Georgetown University, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Glick and Weintraub, P. C., 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Guthrie Theater, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Hartford Stage, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Helen Hayes Awards, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Hispanic Theater Case Study, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - I - J, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Independent Committee on Arts Policy, 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Jones, James Earl, 1984-1991 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - K - L, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Long Wharf Theatre, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - M - N, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Medical Education for South African lacks, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Mercy College, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Morrison, Toni, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - NAACP, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - National Arts Club, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - National Black Theatre Festival, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - National Endowment for the Arts
    - First Amendment, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Armstrong Letter, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Controversy, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Council Retreat, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Personal, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Where to Write Info., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - New Dramatists, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Night of 100 Stars, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Non-Traditional Casting Project, Inc., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - O - P Praemium Imperiale, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Portland Stage Company, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Princeton University, 1989 OCT (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Q - R, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - S - T, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Smithsonian Institute, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Theater Hall of Fame, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - U - Z, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - UK Lectures on American Theater, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - USIA, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - University of California - San Diego, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - University of Hartford, 1991 MAY (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - WNYC, 1990 APR (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Worldnet Program, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Writer's Market, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Rep V Walk in the Woods, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - A Walk in the Woods - Russia, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - A Walk in the Woods - Post Rep, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Piano Lesson
    - Miscellaneous, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Kennedy, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Doolittle, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Walter Kerr Theatre, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Publicity, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - London, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Oprah Winfrey, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Stationery (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Yale Repertory Theatre Study Guide, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Cobb - Atlanta, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Cobb - San Diego, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Rep V - Two Trains Running, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Huntington, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Seattle Rep, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Old Globe, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Post Rep, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Rep I - Ivanov, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Ivanov - Yale Repertory Theatre Study Guide (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Ivanov - Casting, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Rep II - Largo Desolato, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Rep III - Search and Destroy, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Winterfest 11, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Rep IV - Underground, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Rep V Scapin, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Rep VI Moon for the Misbegotten, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Moon for the Misbegotten - O'Neill (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Job Applicants, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Long-Range Academic Plan, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Mailgrams Sent, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Production Calendar, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Production Calendar, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Staff, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Yale Repretory Theatre
    - Accident Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Actors' Directory, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Budget 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Budget 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Company Manager, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - Corporate Committee, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Designers, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Directors, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Dramaturgy Staff, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Program Billing, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Scripts, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Season Brochures, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Yale School of Drama
    - 1989-1990 Students (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - 1989-1990 Student Photos (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - 1990-1991 Students (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Alumni, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Business Office, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Cabaret, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Design Program, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Directing Program, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Dramaturgy Program, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Financial Aid, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - First Year Acting Project, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Humor Project, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Master Teacher Plan, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Meetings with Ben and Earle, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Mordecai, Ben, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - 101's, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Open House 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Personnel, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Playwriting Program, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Registrar, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Safety Committee, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Stage Management Program, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Summer Cabaret, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - TD and P Program, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Theatre Administration Program, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Thesis Projects, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Verse Projects, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Yale University
    - Beinecke Library, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Campus Security, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Commencement, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Yale Development Newsletter, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Development Office, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Fact Files, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - Faculty Outside Activities, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - Financial Aid, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - Financial Reports, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - General Counsel's Office, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - Graduate/Professional Assembly, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Graduate-Professional Student Senate, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Health Services, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Housing, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Local 34, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Law School, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Morse College, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Office of Institutional Research, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Operating Budget, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Provost's Office, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Rodin Report, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Schmidt, Benno, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - Secretary's Office, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - University Auditing, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - Yale Corporation, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Dramaturgy Guide for Lloyd Richards, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Earle and Ben Meeting, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Lloyd Richards
    - Articles, 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Audi File, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Benefits Information, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Callaloo, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Chevrolet File, 1979-1991 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - Departure from YSO/YRT, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Piano Lesson, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Flexible Benefits, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Frequent Flyer Information, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - NEA Personal, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Opening Speech, 1989 September 6 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Piano Lesson Contract, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Recommendations, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Speeches, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Set Designs
    - Pamphlets
    - Videos to Lloyd Richards
    - Magazine Articles on Lloyd Richards, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1991
  - Budget
    - 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 213)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 214 - 215)
  - New Theatre, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 216)
  - Rep Theatre Budget, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 217)
  - Brustein, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 218)
  - Students, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 219)
  - Budget
    - 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 220)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - Cobb, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 222)
  - Assistant to Dean, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Schedule Book, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 224)
  - Appointment Book, 1989-1990
  - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1987 October
  - Budget Committee, 1985 February
  - Yale School of Drama/Repertory Theatre Three Year Budget, 1981-1984
  - Piano Lesson Set Designs (Box 8)
- Records of the dean, 1977-2001; Accession 2011-A-035
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred to MSSA by the Beinecke from the Lloyd Richards papers.
  Arrangement
  Materials are listed alphabetically by folder title.
  Records of the Dean contained in boxes 1 and 2 are restricted until January 1, 2037 due to University policy set by the Yale Corporation. Records of the Dean contained in Box 3 is restricted until January 1, 2067 due to the same University policy.
  - Arrivals, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Materials are restricted until January 1, 2037 due to University policy.
  - Beethoven, Yale School of Music -- Lloyd Richards, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1979-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
    Materials are restricted until January 1, 2067 due to University policy.
  - Budget meeting for 1985-1986, 1985 February (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chairmens committee for 1987-1988, 1987 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - City College of New York (CCNY) Aaron Davis Center, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence
    - S, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - S-W, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10-17)
  - Department chairmen, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Design: costume shop, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Directing, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Drama Productions, Inc., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Drama School Bulletin, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dramaturgs guide, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Dramaturgy, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Additional material, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Faculty concerns, 1978-1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Giamatti, A. Bartlett
    - Correspondence and clipping, 1980-1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - "In Remembrance of Our Friend and Colleague Bart Giamatti", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Lunch, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - LR history for National Council on the Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Master Teacher Plan, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Multi-year contracts, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Additional material, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - New Haven Register, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - New Haven 350th Birthday, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Office notes - needs, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Playwrights
    - Chairperson, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Yale program, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Productions of Chekhov, Ibsen, Shakespeare and Shaw by YRT, LWT, & HSC, Circa 1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Provost
    - 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Memoranda re: sabbatical, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Reading lists, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Reference: thoughts, subjects, ideas, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - "Report on Theater Studies and School of Drama", 1979 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Schmidt, Benno C., 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Soyinka, Wole: "Play of Giants", 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Staff concerns, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stage Blue, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Stage management students, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Student concerns, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Student meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 52-53)
  - TD&P sound, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Theater administration class, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Tony Awards Playbill and pamphlet, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Training, history, and assessment, Circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - University theatre, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Whiting Writers' Award Ceremony invitation, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Winterfest 10, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Yale Endowment Plan "Report to the President", 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Yale Repertory Theater
    - "Cobb," by Lee Blessing, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Contracts, 1982-1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - "Miss Julie", 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Pending projects, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - New York Times publicity, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - "Solid Gold Cadillac", 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Special projects, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Title index to YRT productions, 1966-1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Yale University and New Haven, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Yale University statements - notes, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Yale 300 anniversary, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)